(Bernadette:)Okay, I guess I should
eat the Hell Prawn.
(Sheldon:)Using your sword,
(Sheldon:)you prepare a beautiful
sushi dinner.
(Sheldon:)You slip into the hot spring
and enjoy the warm water
(Sheldon:)on your aching joints.
(Sheldon:)As you happily
close your eyes,
(Sheldon:)you recall the incredible
evening you've had
(Sheldon:)and notice that your...
(die clinks)
(Sheldon:)...feet and ankles are
smaller than they've ever been.
(Sheldon:)The end.
(Bernadette:)Wow, this night turned out to be
so much more fun than I thought.
(Sheldon:)Oh, the fun doesn't stop.
(Sheldon:)You're still going home
with a goodie bag full of toast.
(Bernadette:)Thank you for this.
(Bernadette:)You know, ever since people
found out I'm having a baby,
(Bernadette:)I feel like I became
Pregnant Bernadette.
(Bernadette:)It was nice to take
a little break tonight.
(Sheldon:)I can understand that.
(Sheldon:)From the moment
people realized I was a genius,
(Sheldon:)I've been Sheldon the Genius.
(Sheldon:)Although I've never really
wanted a break from that,
(Sheldon:)so I suppose I don't understand.
(Sheldon:)Which is ironic
(Sheldon:)'cause, you know, genius.
(chuckles)